jamglue.com 2009-08-31

# Jamglue - Privacy Policy

Jamglue, Inc. ("Jamglue") has developed this Privacy Policy ("Policy") in a continued effort to protect the privacy of our users. This Policy is included in and a part of our Terms of Service ("Terms"). Therefore, please refer to our Terms in addition to this Policy. This Policy applies to your use of our website http://jamglue.com and any related services (the "Website"). 

  * Acceptance of Policy 
    * By using or visiting the Website you agree to be bound by this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use the Website.
  * Entire Agreement 
    * The Terms and Privacy Policy are hereby included by reference. They comprise of the entire agreement between you and the Website and govern your use of the Website, superseding any prior agreements between you and the Website.
  * Modifications to Policy 
    * Jamglue reserves the right to change or modify the Policy at any time, without prior notice, by posting the modified Policy on the Website. Your continued use of the Website indicates your acceptance of any revised Policy.
  * Notice 
    * Jamglue may provide you with notifications that include, without limitation, any changes that are made to the Policy or other Website related service, by postings on the Website or via email to a user.
  * Information Gathered 
    * Information Submitted by a user 
      * Jamglue collects personal information when you register or request information from us. The personal information we collect is listed below: 
        * Login Name
        * Password
        * Email address
        * Name
        * Postal Code
        * Home Page
        * Musical Details (Instruments Played, Recording Gear, Recording Label)
      * You may also submit information about other people. For example, you may enter a friend's email to invite to Jamglue, or share a track or mix. In this circumstance, we collect the following information about the recipient: 
        * Email address
    * Non-submitted Information Collected 
      * The Website may also collect non-personal information not associated with your identity. We collect this data to improve the Website. The non-submitted information we collect is listed below: 
        * IP
        * Time
        * File
        * Data transferred
        * Browser type and version
        * Operating system
        * Cookies
      * In addition, to better tailor the Website and to improve our products we may also gather additional information including, but not limited to, demographics, preferences, and experiences with our products or the Website. Giving this data to us will be optional.
  * Information Uses 
    * Use of the Submitted Information 
      * We will not sell or rent Your personal information to others, except to the extent necessary to fulfill any requests by You to share content through another Website or partner.
      * Jamglue may disclose Your information to third parties who are providing services to Jamglue and to our business partners who may provide joint product and service offerings to our Users.
      * Your email can be used to answer any requests made by you, or to provide status updates around the Website or its processes.
      * As a User, You may be able to invite guests to listen to your tracks or mixes online. When you do, we will send an email with the URL to your content to your designated list of recipients. Please note that your guests can then forward that email to other parties. We do not use the email addresses you provide for any other purpose.
      * You may be able to register to receive updates and promotions, or to be contacted for surveys. The contact information you submit will not be used for these purposes unless you specifically opt in. You can control your privacy preferences regarding such marketing communications (see Section 5 below entitled "user's privacy settings and opting out").
      * Jamglue may combine Your information with other information about You that Jamglue receives from other sources.
      * Jamglue may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to Jamglue and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
    * Finally, we do not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above, without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out. 
      * We may use browser detection, IP addresses, operating system detection, time, file type, data transfer detection and cookies to provide a better experience for you. None of the data derived from these technologies is tied to your personally identifiable information. We detect the type of web browser you are using to optimize the performance of the Website. To better understand how people use our site, we may review files and data transferred. IP addresses determine the physical location of a computer. Cookies are files sometimes put onto your computer when you visit Website[s]. These help identify you so that we may better tailor your experience with your interests.
  * Data security 
    * Access to Your data is limited to our authorized staff and restricted by password protection mechanisms.
  * Children's privacy 
    * Jamglue follows the guidelines established by the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). Therefore, we will never knowingly accept or solicit personally identifiable information from a user known to be under the age of thirteen (13). If you have a concern, please refer to our Privacy Policy for information on how to notify us.
  * User's privacy settings and the ability to opt out 
    * How to opt out 
      * We may send marketing communications to Users. If you do not want to receive these updates, you must opt-out by un-checking the "I would like to receive email updates" box on the registration page, or should you choose to opt-out after registering, you can do the following: 
        * Sign in to your Jamglue account, view your profile, edit your profile and uncheck the "Send me Jamglue news" checkbox.
    * How to access or change user information 
      * Simply sign in to your Jamglue account and select "edit my profile."
    * Legal disclaimer disclosure 
      * We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website.
    * Links to Third Party Web Sites 
      * We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Website nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of the Website, or provided by our users to give you more information about themselves. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. By your browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link on the Website, is subject to that website's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.
